Guide to the Burton Avery Noble letters to Lois Scoopmire
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Burton Avery Noble letters to Lois Scoopmire
1921-1924
SC1238
Noble, Burton Avery.
1 Linear feet
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
Burton Avery Noble earned an AB in Chemistry from Stanford University in 1925. While at Stanford, Noble frequently penned letters to his girlfriend Lois Scoopmire, who lived in Gallup, New Mexico. After graduating Noble and Scoopmire were married on June 16, 1926.
Scope and Contents
Letters from Burton Avery Noble to Lois Scoopmire, 1921-1924.
Access Terms
Scoopmire, Lois
Collection Contents
- Letters, Accession ARCH.2015-047
  - 1921 Feb 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1921 Mar 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1921 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1921 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1921 Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1921 Jul 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1921 Jul 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1921 Jul 19 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1921 Jul 20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1921 Jul 21 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1921 Jul 22 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1921 Aug 9 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1921 Aug 10 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1921 Aug 13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1921 Aug 11 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1921 Aug 17 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1921 Aug 24 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1921 Aug 28 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1921 Sep 18 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1921 Oct 9 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1921 Oct 14 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1921 Oct 17 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1921 Oct 20 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1921 Nov 26 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1921 Nov 29 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1921 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1921 Dec 7 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1921 Dec 11 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1921 Dec 23 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1922 Jan 18 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1922 Jan 23 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1922 Feb 6 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1922 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1922 Feb 18 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1922 Apr 17 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1922 Feb 26 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1922 Mar 14 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 1922 Apr 4 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 1922 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 1922 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1922 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 1922 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 1922 May 27 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1922 Jun 4 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1922 Jun 18 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 1922 Jun 26 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 1922 Jun 12 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 1923 Jan 15 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 1923 Feb 19 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 1923 Apr 7 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1923 Apr 24 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1923 Apr 28 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 1923 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 1923 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 1923 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1923 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 1923 Jun 3 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 1923 Jun 13 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 1923 Jun 18 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 1923 Jul 14 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 1923 Jul 16 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 1923 Jul 20 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 1923 Jul 21 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 1923 Aug 23 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 1923 Aug 27 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 1923 Sep 18 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 1923 Sep 19 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 1923 Sep 22 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 1923 Sep 23 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 1923 Sept. 28 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1923 Nov 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1923 Dec 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1923 Nov 26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1923 Dec 6 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1923 Dec 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1923 Dec 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1923 Dec 21 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1923 Dec 31 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1924 Jan 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1924 Jan 6 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1924 Jan 16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1924 Jan 23 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1924 Jan 26 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1924 Jan 27 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1924 Feb 14 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1924 Jan 19 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1924 Feb 26 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1924 Feb 29 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1924 Mar 4 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1924 Mar 7 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1924 Mar 18 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1924 Apr 17 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1924 Apr 2 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 1924 Apr 8 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1924 Apr 15 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1924 Apr 17 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1924 Apr 28 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1924 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1924 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1924 Jun 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1924 Jun 3 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 1924 Jun 9 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1924 Jun 17 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 1924 Jun 21 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1924 Jun 24 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 1924 Jul 4 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 1924 Jul 7 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 1924 Jul 9 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 1924 Jul 15 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 1924 Jul 20 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 1924 Jul 23 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 1924 Jul 28 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 1924 Jul 30 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 1924 Aug 2 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 1924 Aug 4 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 1924 Aug 5 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 1925 Aug 24 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 1924 Sept 4 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 1924 Sept 6 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 1924 Oct 8 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 1924 Oct 8 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 1924 Oct 15 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 1924 Oct 20 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)